cointent.com 2016-04-23

# Privacy Policy | CoinTent

#### Effective as of March 12, 2014

### INTRODUCTION

This Privacy Policy describes your privacy rights regarding our collection, use, storage, sharing and protection of your personal information. We take your privacy and the privacy of our publishers very seriously. Please read this Privacy Policy to learn more about how CoinTent Inc. (“CoinTent,” “we,” our,” or “us”) treats information, including personally identifiable information when you visit our website located at https://cointent.com (this “Site”) or a publisher site that is selling content using CoinTent’s services. We provide this Privacy Policy because you have a right to know what information we collect, how it is protected and used, and the circumstances under which it may be disclosed. If you have comments, suggestions, questions, or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us via email at [support@cointent.com](mailto:support@cointent.com).

### What This Policy Covers

This policy covers the ways in which CoinTent treats information, including personally identifiable information, which we obtain when you use the CoinTent. We regard personally identifiable information as information that someone can use to identify or contact you in person, such as your real name, telephone number, birth date, email address, or physical mailing address. Information that we use internally to identify you as a user in our system is not considered personally identifiable information. This policy does not cover privacy practices of third parties, such as the Publishers we work with, or third-party payment process services.

### How We Collect Information

##### Information Provided By CoinTent consumers.

Content consumers must create an account with CoinTent to access content through our services. To create an account we will require your email address and will send you an email to that address to confirm you are the owner of that email address. If you choose to fund your account you will need to provide payment information. If you fund your account with a credit card, CoinTent may collect your credit card number; expiration date; name on the credit card; card security code, zip/postal code; and physical address.

### Editing / Deleting Account Information.

##### Account access:

Any user who creates a CoinTent account can view the personally identifiable information we have collected from that user by logging in on our website and viewing their account page. To completely delete your account and accompanying personal information, please contact us at [support@cointent.com](mailto:support@cointent.com).

### Information We Do Not Collect From Any Users

##### Children.

 As explained further in our Consumer Terms of Service and Publisher Terms of Service, you must be 18 years of age or older – or, if you are under the age of majority in your jurisdiction, have the consent of your parent or guardian – to use the CoinTent Service. Therefore, we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information about children. In accordance with Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), CoinTent will never knowingly solicit, nor will we accept, personally identifiable information from users known to be under thirteen (13) years of age. If you believe that we have information from or about anyone under 13 years of age, please notify us by email at [support@cointent.com](mailto:support@cointent.com).

##### Social Security Number.

 We do not require your social security number to use the CoinTent Service or to access any part of our site. CoinTent will never ask for your social security number except in the course of required tax documentation prior to publisher payments.

### Information We Track

##### Log Files.

 Similar to many websites and internet services, we gather certain anonymous, non-personal information automatically and store it in web server log files. This information includes internet protocol addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), site entry/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click stream data. We use this information to improve our site, analyze trends, administer the site, and gather aggregate information about our user base as a whole. Aggregate information is data we collect about a group or category of services or users from which individual user identities have been removed, and therefore does not include your personally identifiable information. Of course, if you complete transactions through the CoinTent site, we will collect and track payment information so that we can properly pay our publisher partners.

##### Cookies.

 A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record- keeping purposes. It can also help us understand how our site visitors click to our site, what pages they view during their visit, and their account and preference information as users of the CoinTent Service. Similar to many websites, the CoinTent Service stores an encrypted cookie on your computer so we can remember you when you come back without requiring you to log in each time. Cookies also allow us to track and understand the interests of our users to enhance the overall experience on our site. Cookies used by CoinTent do not include your personally identifiable information

If you prefer not to receive cookies, you can set your web browser software to disable them. To do so, please refer to the help section of your specific browser for more information on how to manage or disable cookies. Please note that your browser must be configured to accept cookies to use the CoinTent Service.

### HOW WE USE INFORMATION

##### Information Use:

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a secure, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. We may use your personal information to:

  * provide CoinTent Services and customer support;
  * process transactions and send notices about your transactions;
  * resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Terms;
  * customize, measure, and improve CoinTent Services and the content, layout, and operation of our websites and applications;
  * deliver targeted marketing, service update notices, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences.

### HOW WE SHARE AND DISCLOSE INFORMATION

##### With Third-Parties.

We share your personally identifiable information, i.e. user name and email address, with Publishers that use the CoinTent Service to make their content available to Consumers. We do so because when a Consumer purchases content from one of our Publisher partners they are in effect acting as a customer of the Publisher. Your data is co-owned with the Publisher and CoinTent.

Occasionally we share anonymous, non-personal, aggregate information about our user base with partners or advertisers, and we may publish these aggregate usage statistics on our website for the interest of our users. We do not tie this shared or published data to the personally identifiable information of any person.

##### As Necessary In Certain Legal Circumstances.

 We reserve the right to disclose your information, including personally identifiable information, when we have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is necessary to (a) comply with any law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce this Privacy Policy, including investigation of potential violations of this Privacy Policy, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of CoinTent, its users, or the public as required or permitted by law.

##### Acquisition.

 If CoinTent becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, including bankruptcy, our assets, including user information, may be transferred to a third party. At that time, your user information may become subject to that third party’s privacy policy. Before we transfer your user information, we will notify you either by email or by posting a prominent notice on our site, and we will remind you of your ability to add, edit or delete your personally identifiable information from your account management options page in advance of any such transfer.

### HOW WE KEEP INFORMATION SECURE

##### Network Security.

 We use commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard and secure your personal information while stored on our computer systems. We have implemented a variety of industry standard encryption and security technologies and procedures to protect your information, including your personal information, stored in our computer systems from unauthorized access. Please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, thus we strive to use commercially reasonable means to protect your personal information, but we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

##### Management Procedures.

 We also maintain industry standard physical and electronic procedural safeguards that limit access to your personally identifiable information to our employees (or people working on our behalf and under confidentiality agreements) who, through the course of standard business activities, need to access your personally identifiable information.

### UPDATES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

We may amend this policy at any time by posting a revised version on our website. The revised version will be effective at the time we post it. In addition, if the revised version includes a substantial change, we will provide notice of the changes prominently on this page of our website.

### How you can contact us about privacy questions

If you have questions or concerns with this policy please contact us at [support@cointent.com](mailto:support@cointent.com).
